

# **ABOUT ME**

I am a Full Stack Developer from Peru living in Spain. My interest in technology and involvement with it go back as far as I can remember. After years experience in Marketing and Sales, I made the best decision to turn my hobby into my profession.

# **SKILLS**

HTML5 Docker CSS3 MySQL SASS Gulp Git Javascript React Js Agile Express Js Scrum Ejs Slack MongoDB Canva

#### SOFTSKILLS

TeamWork Client Focus Attention to Empathy detail Problem Solving Adaptability Quick Positive

attitude

LANGUAGES

learner

Spanish **English** Native Professional

# Francesca Bentin

Full Stack Developer

+34 635475139

francescabentin@gmail.com

 $\oplus$  francescabentin.github.io/portfolio/  $\Box$ 





## **EXPERIENCE**

Adalab | Remote | January. 2023 - April 2023

Full-Stack Developer

- Layout: HTML5, CSS3, Sass, Responsive Design, Flexbox, CSS Grid.
- Javascript (ES6) and creation of a SPA with React.
- Developing a basic API with Node JS and Express JS.
- · Version control with Git.
- Project development under SCRUM; framework and Agile philosophy.
- Development tools: Gulp, Visual Studio Code. Terminal, Zeplin, Render.
- Communication skills and team work: Slack, Github.

**Booksy Spain | 2022** Sales Consultant

Travelling | 2019 Personal experience

**British American Tobacco** Lima | 2016 - 2018 Trade Marketing rep

Mondelez Spain. | 2020 - 2021 Trade marketing rep

**Enterprise Rent a car Mallorca** 

Customer and sales agent

Cool Trends | 2014 - 2016 Account manager

Kimbery Clark | 2011 - 2013 Trade marketing rep

# **EDUCATION**

Web Development Bootcamp Adalab | 2023 **Business Administration** University of lima | 2009 - 2014

## LATESTS PROJECTS



Website for a Brand, Personal project HTML, CSS, SASS



Presentation cards Apil HTML, CSS, SASS, Javascript, gulp





Harry Potter fan search Apil HTML, CSS, SASS,REACT





Proyects data manager Apil HTML, CSS, REACT, Node Js, Express, SQL, render por deployment





Hangman Game Api | HTML, CSS, SASS, REACT, NPM